Guide to the Delmer Daves Papers, 1930-1965
Department of Special Collections
- A Summer Place Pt. II
  - Data for records on A Summer Place., 3/23/59
  - IOC-S MacEwen to Obringer re: firing dialogue director Bert Steiner. C., 4/17/59; 8vo.
  - IOC Bill Hendricks to DD re: pre-release screening. M., 9/23/59; 8vo.
  - IOC HF (secretary to DD) to publicity dept. re: publicity stills for DD's private collection., 11/3/59
- Fan letters
  - ALS Phil Davis to DD with envelope (Gt. Britain)., 3/8/60; 6 3/4" × 9". (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - TNC answer to above., 5/2/60
  - ALS Susan Owens to DD., 2/27/60
  - TLC DD to Susan Owens-answer., 5/2/60
  - ALS Randall Haynes to DD re: trying to get screen test for friend., 3/24/60
  - TLC DD to Randall Haynes re: answer., 5/2/60
  - TLS Cecil Doll to DD re: fan letter., 3/31/60; 8vo.
  - TLC DD to Cecile Doll; re: answer., 5/2/60
  - ALS Mildred Krutsch to DD re: school report., 5/6/60
  - TLC DD to Mildred Krutsch re: answer., 6/20/60
  - Judy Hodges to DD. ALS., 8/6/61
- Miscellaneous
  - Staff and cast list with addresses and telephone numbers., 2/19/59; 3 copies, M. 2 pgs. each. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Final billing set-up. M., 5/14/59; 2 pgs. 8" X 12 1/2" taped edd on end. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Adaptation notes., 10/4/58; 6 pgs (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Sequence outline., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Shooting schedule. Purple ink reproduction., 2/13/59; 2 pgs. 17" × 28". (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Cast selection information, lists, and publicity, with FPNAD., ND; 24 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - LA Times reviews of movie., 10/11/59 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Group photograph of cast and crew., ND (Box 51, Folder 15)
- LA Times review., ND/11/59 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Index to breakdown and breakdown of sequences. M., 1/7/59; 138 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Shooting schedule for interior and exterior scenes. M., ND; 46 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Total cost, set by set breakdown and description., ND; 2 pgs (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - IOC Leo K. Kuter to C. Greenlaw re: using existing sets in movie, with 2C. pg. list of sets to be built and sets to be remoddled., 12/31/58; 3 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Staging for automobile breakdown. M., 1/12/59 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Preliminary survey party travel itinerary to Monterey., ND (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - AN on production dialogue, etc.., ND; 8vo. 10 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Daily production report for 2/2/59, 2/4/59, and 2/16/59. C., ---; 3 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous PN on production., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Script changes. M., 3/20/59; 4 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - IOC George Grove to [all concerned] re: posting [UNK] retakes., 3/3/59-4/23/59; 24 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Placemat and brochure from Hotel Hunras., ND (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Location and set diagrams. P., ND; 7 pgs. (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Xerox maps of location., ND; 33 pgs. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Complete shooting script and cutting notes with FPpNAD and P sketches, 2/16/59; (ca. 130 pgs, 8 per pg., 1 3/4" × 2 1/2").. Ca. 140 pgs. both sides. (Box 52, Folder 2,3)
    Folder 2, beginning to p.50; Folder 3, p. 51 on
- Parrish Pt. I (WB), 1959-1960
  - Original novel cut up and pasted on paper with extensive PNAD., ND; ca. 90 pgs. both sides. (Box 52, Folder 4,5)
  - 1st rough draft SP by DD with FPNAD., 12/2/59; ca. 200 pgs. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - 2nd draft SP by DD with FPNAD. M., 12/2/59; 156 pgs. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Final draft SP with OPNAD. M., 1/16/60; 143 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Rev. final SP with PNAD., 2/11/60; 142 pgs. M. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - General Sequence outline with 1 pg. foreword in pen., ND; 9 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Sequence outline with emphasis on love, characters, sex., ND (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Script development notes. P., ND; 12 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - TLS Mildred Savage to DD re: script changes., 12/25/59; 3 pgs. 8vo. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - TLS Mildred Savage to DD re: more script changes., 12/30/59; 4 pgs.
  - TLS Mildred Savage to DD re: comments., 1/7/60; 2 pgs
  - ALS Mildred Savage to DD re: comments on 2nd section., 1/18/60; 5 pgs
  - ALS Mildred Savage to DD re: tightening script., 2/22/60; 4 pgs
  - TLS Mildred Savage to DD re: approval of rev. final script., 3/10/60; 8vo.
  - Notebook of photographs from Connecticut location., ND; ca. 50 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Parrish
  - Staff and cast list (2 copies) with addresses and tlelphone numbers., 5/5/60; M. - 1 pg. 8vo. and T. -4 pgs.. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - List of actors with P notes., 4/21/60; 4 pgs.
  - Rev. final script changes. M., 6/14/60; 5 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Shooting schedule and location notes for Hartford, Conn., with OPNAD. M, 7/6/60; 10 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Production notes for on location shooting with OPNAD. M., 4/6/60; 7 pgs. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Principal photography list for location in Windsor area., ND; 13 pgs.
  - Post-production and location (Windsor area) information. M., ND; 2 pgs. with P sketch on vso. of pg. 1. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Complete shooting time schedule, purple ink mimeograph, with FPN., ND; 2 pgs., 1 pg. 22" × 17" and 1 pg. 16½" × 17". (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Location maps, drawings and floor plans. Blue print., ND; 51 pgs. with 1 pg. 16" × 11" and 2 pgs. 16" × 22". (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Map of Windsor area with PN on location. Printed., ND; 39" × 50". (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - TL-verifax copy with PNAD Shurlock to JLW re: censors' comments., 1/29/60; 2 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Same as #7a, 2/3/60; 2 pgs.
  - Same as #7a, 2/23/60; 3 pgs.
  - Same as #7a, 3/29/60; 1 pg. C.
  - Notice of tentative writing credits. C., 6/24/60 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Data sheet for records. C., 6/27/60
  - Rev. movement list for Conn. locations., 5/3/60; 8 pgs (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Dialogue revisions and check list on revising script and translating novels to SP., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Itemized list for wardrobe expenses for C. Colbert at Saks 5th Ave.., ND; Size X. 2 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - List of tobacco growers in Conn. and misc. contacts, with PNAD., ND (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - IOC-S T. Buchanon to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing notes for trailer scene and scene itself. C., 8/3/60 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Trailer scene with FPNAD., ND
  - Misc. Pp notes and sketches., ND; 4 pgs. both sides plus 3 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Rev. final SP by DD-complete shooting script with diagrams and scene sketches, 2/10/60; ca. 130 pgs., 8/pg., 1 3/4" × 2½"). M., with FPpNAD. 143 pgs. of script. (Box 54, Folder 9,10)
    9 to p. 66
    10 p. 6709
- Parrish
  - Folder A
    - Staff list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 5/5/60 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Cast list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 5/5/60
    - List of casting options., ND; 2 pgs.
    - 8" × 10" photograph of Connie Stevens. BW., ND (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Final and Rev. final cast lists with character descriptions., ND; 6 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - IOC-S Hoyt Bowers to Greenlaw-Bau-Hiatt-Schweibert re: screen test schedule., 5/2/60 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Biographical information on actors and actresses interviewed., 2/24/60; 7 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Fan club postcard photo(color) of Troy Donahue., ND; 4" × 6". (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Biography of Sharon Hugueny. M., ND; 2 pgs. 2 copies. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Biography of Diane McBain. M., ND; 2 pgs. 3 copies. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - 3 Test scenes (last 1=2 copies). M., ND; 10 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Memo DD to HF re: duplicating test scenes., 3/1/60 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - IOC HF to Print shop re: print up test scene., 3/1/60
    - 3 test scenes, original., ND; 9 pgs.
    - Cancellations for Parrish screening, with PN., ND (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Acceptance list-C with pN. Original and copy with PpNAD., ND; 2 pgs.
    - IOC HF to E. L. de Pattie re: guest lists attached. C., 2/7/61; 8vo.
    - Misc. notes with PAD., 2/7/61; 4¼" × 6 1/8".
    - Guest list for 2/7/61 screening., ND
    - IOC HF to R. Tafayre re: attached 2 guest list., 1/26/61
    - IOC HF to E. L. de Pattie re: guest list., 1/26/61
    - Same as #13a-original., ND
    - Acceptance List for Proj. 12., ND; 3 pgs.
    - Acceptance list for for Proj. room 5. C., ND; 2 copies.
    - ANS Pat to HF re: clearing gate., 1/26/61
    - IOC-S HF to E.L. de Pattie re: wants to show print., 1/18/61; 2 copies.
  - Folder B
    - Set construction cost list., 5/6/60; 10" × 14". (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Women's wardrobe plot, pgs. 15 - 18. M., ND (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Mens and women's wardrobe plot., 4/4/60; 2 copies. 41 pgs. each. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Index to and breakdown of scenes. M., 4/7/60; 107 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Folder C
    - Pre-production and production information for on location filming. M., 4/6/60; 22 pgs. 2 copies. (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Movement list for 3rd Hartford locations with pN., 7/8/60; 4 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Itinerary for DD. C., ND (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Location information sheet for filmming unit., 4/29/60 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Tentative movement list for Conn. locations. M., 4/28/60; 6 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Rev. tentative movement list for Conn. locations. M., 5/30/60; 8 pgs.
    - Movement list for 3rd Hartford locations., 7/8/60; 2 copies, 4 pgs eachs
    - Hartford, Conn., locations for 3rd trip. M., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - TLS Frank P. Morse to DD re: wants them to stay at Statler Hilton., 1/11/60; Size X. (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - TLS Frank P. Morse to DD re: will have rooms ready for them on return., 4/26/60; Size X.
    - TLC DD to Frank P. Morse re: travel and accomodation arrangements., 4/28/60
    - TLS F. P. Morse to DD re: answer to #7c., 5/3/60; Size X.
    - Correspondence between Ralph C. Lasbury Jr., Windsor Hill, Conn., and DD re: contracting local farmers and their farms for filming., 5/30/60
      - a. 4/26/60TLS R. C. Lasbury to DD.
      - b. 4/27/60TLS R. C. Lasbury to DD
      - c. 4/28/60TLC DD to R. C. Lasbury
      - d. 4/29/60TLC DD to R. C. Lasbury, 2 pgs.
  - Folder D
    - Shooting schedule for all WB productions M., 4/13/60-7/21/60; 60 pgs. front and vso. (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Daily call sheets, M., 6/7/60-7/12/60; 23 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Folder E
    - Itemized weekly production costs., 4/23/60-6/18/60; 14 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - List of expense accounts., 4/18/60; 11" × 11". 2 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Daily production and progress report. C., 3/4/60-7/22/60; 53 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Folder F
    - IOC-S Hal Hohlman to DD re: expense advances., 11/2/59; 8vo. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - IOC HF to Hal Hohlman re: above. C., 11/10/59
    - IOC HF to Jay Goetzman re: replacing furniture., 11/10/59; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to Hal Hehlman re: personal financial reimbursement. C., 12/15/59; 8vo.
    - TLS DD to HF re: personal accounts and rock collection., 12/14/59; Size X.
    - IOC-S HF to Fred Pappmeier re: personal financial reimbursement., 1/18/60; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to J. A. Smith re: pick up script., 1/14/60; 8vo.
    - IOC-S HF to Tom Murphy re: approval for mileage and overtime to pick up script., 1/18/60
    - IOC DD to Trilling, Greenlaw, and Bowers re: Conn. location shooting dates and production scheduling. C., 1/19/60; 2 pgs.
    - IOC HF to Johnny O'Steen re: script., 1/19/60; 8vo. C.
    - IOC HF to Jo Glendon re: Mimeographing script. C., 11/30/59; 8vo.
    - TNHF to Jo Glendon re: sending script in 3 parts., 11/18/59; 3" × 5".
    - IOC HF to Trilling re: minor word and direction changes. C., 3/24/60; 8vo.
    - IOC C. Greenlaw to all dept. re: pre-production meeting., 4/8/60
    - IOC C. Greenlaw to all dept. re: budget meeting for movie. C., 4/27/60; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to Meta Rebner re: word change in script. C., 5/6/60; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to Johnny O'Steen re: enclosing materials for file. C., 8/10/60; 8vo.
    - Store requisition receipts., 5/10/60+11/10/59; 2 pgs.
    - Records of scripts received., 1/16/60
  - Folder G
    - ALS and TLS with C. answers--10 fan letters for Parrish and A Summer Place., --- (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - ALS and TLS unanswered fan mail., --- (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - ALS and TLS 5 applications (answered) for position on WB staff., --- (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - ALS and TLS 11 applications by local Conn. acting talent for small parts (business and personal)., --- (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - TLS Wolfram L. Lewis to DD re: personal-wishes to know arrangements for Parrish., 4/25/60; Siz X. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - TLC DD to Wolfram L. Lewis re: answer to above., 4/29/60
    - TLC HF to C. Colbert re: enclosing script changes., 4/27/60; 3vo.
    - Telegram DD to Colbert re: picture of herself., 4/28/60; 8vo.
    - TLS Frederic Lynch to DD re: has large home which may be used for filming., ND
    - TLC DD to F. W. Lynch, Jr. re: answer to above., 5/2/60
    - TLC DD to Sam Lawrence Jr. re: [UNK] music lyrics., 5/3/60
    - ALS Ellen Corby to DD re: personal., 5/7/60; 6 1/4" × 7".
    - TLC HF to Ellen Corby re: answer to above., 5/9/60
    - TLC Harry Mayer to Vivienne Nearing re: contract for free lance-D. Knapp., 5/16/60
    - TLS Dale Olson to DD re: advertising-filled out form and envelope., 6/14/60
    - TLC HF to Dale Olson re: no., 6/20/60; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to Troy Donahue re: clearing up scandal of woman who ran away from husband with baby to come to Hollywood., 6/23/60; 8vo.
    - TLS Meta Rebner to DD re: personal., 7/28/60
    - TLC HF to Saundra Edwards, Karl Malden, Fred Marlon, C. Colbert (4 separate letters) re: enclosing Parrish group picture., 8/4/60; 8vo.
    - TLC DD to Charles Boyd re: thanks for Parrish promotional efforts., 8/9/62
    - TLS Capt. Milton Dickinson to DD re: personal., 10/27/60
    - TLS Arthur W. Lenzi to DD re: thanks for help., 10/28/60
    - IOC HF to Kenny Sebo re: several film cuttings to the Loomis School., 12/12/60; 2 copies. C. 8vo.
    - TLC DD to Mrs. R. Erickson re: enclosing film strip and thanks for help., 12/12/60; 2 copies.
    - TLS Doris Rockwell to DD re: wants to know when premiere is., 1/12/61
    - TLS Marjorie Bennett to DD re: Wants to work for DD., 10/3/61
    - ACS Meta Rebner to HF re: personal regards., 5/24/60
    - List of phone calls and messages., ND; 8" × 9!1/2#.
    - Lyrics to poem or song., ND
- Susan Slade (WB), 1960-1961
  - Daily production and progress reports., 10/26/60-2/3/61; [UNK] C. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Folder 1
    - Casting suggestion selection list with PN. C., 10/3/60 (Folder 12)
    - Final cast and staff list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 11/2/60
    - Rev. index to breakdown and breakdown of sequences. M. 109 pgs. Incomplete., 10/25/60 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Portraits of Connie Stevens - 1 3"×5" color, 2 8" × 10" BW., ND (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Biography of Connie Stevens. M, ND; 3 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - 14 IOC Graves to all dept. re: post-synchronization retakes. C., 12/17/60-12/27/60; 8vo. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - IOC DD to Tom Buchanan re: enclosing original and 2 copies of suggested trailer. C., 1/11/61; 39 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Carbon copy of above., 1/11/61; 5 pgs.
  - Folder 2
    - Shooting schedule. M, 11/8/60-1/5/61; 44 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Locations information sheet for Monterey and San Francisco. M., 11/4/60; 2 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Movement list. M., 11/4/60; 7 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Trona location movement list. M., 12/29/60; 2 copies, 2 pgs. each.
    - Airline schedules to Monterey., ND
    - WB shooting schedule for all productions. M., 11/8/60-1/3/61; 36 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Call sheets for actors. M., 11/29/60-1/3/60; 26 pgs. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Folder 3
    - TLC HF to Golden Gate Bridge Authority re: payment for filming on bridge., 12/15/60 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - IOC HF to E. J. O'Carroll re: enclosing statement from bridge authority. C., 12/15/60; 8vo.
    - Statement of expenses incurred by DD while in San Francisco. C., 12/8/60; 2 copies. 3 pgs.
    - IOC-S HF to San Pasqua re: enclosing personal statement. C., 12/8/60; 2 copies. 2 pgs.
    - Original record and memo for #2. 1 pg. 5" × 7", 1 pg. regular, and 2 pgs. Size X., 12/2/60
    - 3 hotel bills, Sheraton Palace, San Francisco., 10/23/60; 6 1/4" C 6 3/4". (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Campus Camera Shop receipt., 10/15/60; 16mo.
    - 3 1/2" × 6" receipt for Avis-Rent-A-Car., ND
  - Folder 4
    - ALS and TLS-16 letters answered by HF-fan mail., ND (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Review of Susan Slade in Memphis Press Schmitar with accompanying explanatory card and envelope., 11/16/61 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Folder 5.
    - IOC HF to Joe Barry re: enclosing 2 geological survey maps., 1/10/60; 8vo. (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - IOC Bill L. Hendricks to Steve Trilling re: production information on Deathmaker. C., 10/5/60
    - TLC John Alton to DD re: unable to accept offer., 10/6/60
    - TLS Meta Rebner to DD re: desire to work., 10/11/60
    - ALS both sides Lt. Maurice R. Reardon to DD re: photographing Spreckels Mansion., 10/11/60
    - TLS Cecilia Cremer to DD re: photographing mansion., 10/13/60
    - Enclosing note-returned by Joe Barry., 12/21/60; 3" × 5".
    - TLS Robert Cleaves to DD re: possible cast opening., 10/16/60; 5" × 8"
    - TLS Robert Cleaves to DD re: thanking him for answering., 10/18/60; 5" × 8 in.
    - TLS Patricia Burton to DD re: Capt. Topper-prize Shetland stallion., 10/18/60
    - ALS Susan Slade to DD re: coincidence of names., 10/19/60
    - TLS Joe Manchester to DD re: getting plays written for Manchester Productions., 10/26/60
    - IOC Carl Milliken jr. to DD re: clearance of proper names. M., 10/27/60
    - TLS Lew Jacobs, Jr. to DD re: seeking approval for article Better Movie Making written by himself., 10/27/60
    - TLS Harold Abramson to DD re: offering information for Red Cross (possible mention in picture)., 10/28/60
    - TLC Shurlock to JLW re: censors' comments on final script., 10/28/60
    - Memo sheet from Walter MacEwen, 4 1/4" × 5", addressed to DD., ND
    - TLS Lee Beinstoc to DD re: wants job as dialogue director., 10/29/60
    - TLS Nagene Searle to DD re: wants job as script footage estimator., 10/31/60
    - TLC DD to Adams (Golden Gate Bridge Authority) re: treatment of traffic problems due to shooting., 11/2/60
    - ? to DD re: working for DD, plus enclosure., 11/14/60
    - List of people from Hartford used for movie,.with PN., ND
    - Mary Lou Daves to HF ALS re: [UNK] addresses requested., ND; 2 pgs. C.
    - TLC HF to Mrs. Daves re: enclosing addresses for above., 11/22/60
    - TLS Jim Sidor to DD re: recommending Monica (friend) for acting., 1/29/60; 2 pgs. 6" × 9".
    - TLC HF to Jim Sidor re: answer to above., ND
    - TLS Hillard Elkins to DD re: recommending Charles Strouse and Lee Adams for composing and lyrics., 12/6/60; 7 1/4" × 8 1/2".
    - TLC HF to Hillard Elkins re: no music or lyrics needed., 12/9/60
    - Telegram Kordovani to DD re: wants to observe American filming techniques., 12/60
    - TLC HF to Kordovani re: affirmative to above., 12/30/60
    - TLS Robert Cleaves to DD re: thanks for part., 1/13/61; 5" × 8".
    - TLS George Stuyvesant to DD re: thanks ofr part., 1/14/61; Size X.
    - TLS John Husted (operator at [T]rona airport to DD re: regards and asks about Susan Slade, with T. note from DD to HF on it., 10/5/61
    - TLC HF to John T. Husted re: answer to above., 10/9/61
    - IOC HF to DD re: enclosing publicity stills (76)., 11/20/61
    - TLS Ricardo H. Boada to DD re: technical error in movie., 3/20/62
    - Tl draft HF to Boada re:answer to above., 3/21/62
    - Sheet with information on American President Lines., ND
    - TLC HF to Boada, see #27b., 3/21/62
    - ALS Judy Klosterman to DD re: finding copy of novel., 3/15/63; 8vo. 2 pgs.
    - TLC HF to Judy Klosterman re: answer to above., 6/4/63
    - TLS Patricia Burton to DD re: requesting unused footage of Capt. Topper., 9/20/63
    - TLC HF to P. Burton re: answer to above., 9/24/63
    - 2-3" × 5" notes asking about negatives., 9/23/63
    - Envelope with newspaper articles., ND (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Physical description of 5 actors., ND (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Hold Harmless Agreement signed by DD-assuming responsibility for accidents at Trona airport while filming., ND (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Trailer opening-publicity short., 5/22/61 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Notice of tentative writing credits., 12/7/60 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Requisition to stores., 11/17/60+11/30/60 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - IOC DD to Trilling re: final script changes., 12/29/60 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - 2 copies of changes., 12/20/63
    - WB Christmas card list., ND (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Susan Slade
  - Outpages from 1st draft, Susan's Sin- SP by DD from novel by Doris Hume., ND; ca. 30 pgs. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Index to breakdown and breakdown of Rev. final script. M., 10/24/60; ca. 25 pgs. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Staff and cast list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 11/2/60 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Final cast list with options for minor roles., ND
  - Interviews with actors with FPpNAD., NDpgs.; 9 pgs.
  - Cast in order of appearance with character descriptions., with pNAD. M., ND; 3 pgs.
  - Synopsis of Susan Slade., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Official record of credits, data for records., 12/19/60 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - IOC Joe Barry to C. Greenlaw re: reservations for accomodations. C., 10/21/60; 8vo. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Location information sheets, M., 11/4/60; 2 pgs.
  - Movement list. M., 11/4/60; 7 pgs.
  - Locations sheet. M., 10/12/60; 2 copies. 4 pgs. each.
  - Index and pgs. 104-105 to breakdown of rev. SP, 10/25/60. M., ND; 3 pgs.
  - Bit list. M., 10/21/60; 2 pgs.
  - Floor plans for SS. Pres. Cleveland and Wilson., ND; 2 copies. 27" × 31 1/2". (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - ANS Ray Obringer to DD re: clearance of names used in script., 11/10/60; 5" × 7".
  - Verifax copies of floor plans for set., ND; 24 pgs.
  - TLS James Adams to DD re: permission and terms for using Golden Gate for shooting purposes., 11/1/60 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - IOC-S Carl Milliken Jr. to Ray Obringer re: using a copyrighted National Geographic photograph. C., 11/9/60
  - TLC Leonard J. Grant to R. J. Obringer re: can't use photo wanted., 11/18/60
  - IOC-S Carl Milliken Jr. to Bill Kuehl re: enclosing above letter-get another picture., 11/21/60
  - ALS Bill Kuehle to DD re: list of things done by writer., Friday; Legal.
  - Test scene for Conn and Susan., ND
  - TL verifax James Jack Jr. to Charles Greenlaw re: proper treatment of animals while filming., 11/4/60
  - Production requisition for help and sets., 12/2/60; Legal.
  - IOC Tom Buchanan to C. Greenlaw re: some plans for trailers in advertisement. C., 1/31/61/
  - TLC G. Shurlock to JLW re: censors' comments., 10/7/60; 2 pgs.
  - IOC-S R. A. Pease to DD re: enclsoing list of vehicle rentals., 1/20/61; 8vo.
  - List of auto, truck rentals at location., 1/20/61
  - Christmas list for Susan Slade crew - C with PN., ND; 2 copies, 2 pgs each.
  - Trailer suggested continuity script by DD. C., ND; 5 pgs.
  - Miscellaneous calling cards, notes and telephone numbers., ND; 10 items. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Data, addresses and notes-people and places involved in move, with OPN., ND; 7 pgs. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Shooting script with sketches, notes, cast list and FPpNAD., ND; 141 pgs. os script, ca. 135 pgs. sketches, 8/ pg., 113/4" × 2 1/2" M. (Box 56, Folder 11,12)
    11 to p. 47
    12 p. 48 on
  - Final script with dubbing notes., 10/24/60; 141 pgs. M. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Estimating script., 9/30/60; 155 pgs. M. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Final script. M., 10/24/60; 141 pgs. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Sin of Susan Slade- Edward Small Productions. M., 3/10/60; 171 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Outline of story beginning., 1/27/60; 3 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Notes., ND; 2 pgs.